# Mafida Tahir

Dubai, Unites Arabs Emirates 00000 | +971558829657 | mufidar2000@gmail.com

## Summary

Motivated and enthusiastic who likes to challenge their abilities and gain valuable experience. I want to utilize my skills and passion to contribute to a company's goals, and to grow both personally and professionally. I thrives in an environment where I take new task and push myself to reach new heights.

Ready to work together and accomplish that mission!

### **Experience**

SMALL BUSINESS OWNER | 06/2022 - 06/2023

Home business - Kano, Nigeria

#### **VOLUNTEER VISA TYPING** | 09/2021 - 02/2022

Red diamon tourism - Dubai, UAE

- Picked up additional tasks to aid team success.
- Inspected products and services to comply with quality standards.

STUDENT | 09/2019 - 09/2021

Middlesex University Dubai - Dubai, UAE

- Likes to challenge my ability.
- · Trying new things and tasks.
- Attended field trips centred on course topics, expanding horizons and knowledge.
- Maintained balance of education, sports and volunteer activities as student.

#### Skills

- · Persuasive information and communication.
- Understanding needs.
- Trying to provide satisfaction.

#### Education

Middlesex University Duba - Dubai, UAE | SVQ Level 1

LLB. Hons., 09/2019 - Current

## Languages

English::	Cl
Advanced	
Arabic::	A2
Elementary	

# **Hobby and interests**

· Hiking, traveling, shopping, spreading love.